{
    "id": "1c145d396c5c4b88be3f299b12a3fefd",
    "title": "Passives Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "bc64b6a3ae744d919de4bbc29caa1381",
            "title": "Passives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The walls ........................................ painted.",
                    "description": "The passive form of the present continuous is used to talk about ongoing actions and situations.",
                    "answers": [
                        "are still",
                        "are still being"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This bag ................................... of leather.",
                    "description": "We use the simple present to talk about materials used for making things.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is made",
                        "was made",
                        "has been made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The smugglers .......................................",
                    "description": "In the present perfect, the passive verb form is: has/have + been + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have caught",
                        "have been caught",
                        "is caught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "All of them ......................................",
                    "description": "In the present perfect, the passive verb form is: has/have + been + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have invited",
                        "have been invited",
                        "have been inviting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boys ...................................... for their performance.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, the passive form is made by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "were praised",
                        "were praising",
                        "have praised"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................... by the manager.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, the passive form is made by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has sacked",
                        "was sacked",
                        "was sacking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The suspect ..................................... by the police.",
                    "description": "We use the present continuous passive to talk about ongoing actions and situations.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is interrogated",
                        "is interrogating",
                        "is being interrogated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ....................................  to the post of manager.",
                    "description": "In the simple future, the passive form is made by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will promote",
                        "will be promoting",
                        "will be promoted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ........................................ to resign.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "forced",
                        "was forcing",
                        "was forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The roof ................................... by the masons.",
                    "description": "The passive form of the present continuous is used to talk about ongoing actions and situations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "is repaired",
                        "is being repaired",
                        "has been repairing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "These tablets ....................................... with food.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "must take",
                        "must be taken",
                        "must be taking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It .................................... from New Zealand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is importing",
                        "is imported",
                        "has imported"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}